phrasemix.com 2017-11-01

# Privacy Policy | PhraseMix.com

##  1\. What information do we collect? 

PhraseMix collects personal information from you from various sources, including: 

  * through this website and others 
  * when you email us or communicate with us through social media 
  * when you participate in PhraseMix events or other promotions 

The types of personal information we may collect include: 

  * Your email address 
  * Your name 
  * Your general location 
  * Your credit card number and other payment details 
  * Other information that you provide to us through direct communication 

We also collect some information automatically when you visit the website or open PhraseMix emails through cookies and web beacons. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. A “web beacon” is a small, transparent graphic that is used to transmit information back to a web server. We also may use third-party website analytics like Google Analytics that collect information about visitors to PhraseMix.com. The information we collect automatically includes: 

  * Information about the devices you use to access the site (such as your IP address and the device, browser and operating system type) 
  * Your browser's language preference information 
  * A general geographic location (such as country and city) from which you are accessing our sites 
  * URLs and search terms that refer visitors to the site 
  * Dates and times of visits to our site 
  * Information about actions taken on the site (such as page views and site navigation patterns) 

##  2\. How do we use your information? 

PhraseMix will use your information to: 

  * Provide services you request and process transactions, including subscription payments. 
  * Send you email communication as requested. 
  * Communicate with you about products, services, and promotions from PhraseMix and our partners. 
  * Respond to your questions and comments. 
  * Improve the quality of the lessons offered by PhraseMix. 
  * Analyze trends and statistics regarding visitors’ use of our sites 
  * Display the website in the language which you will be best able to understand. 
  * Enforce the Terms of Service of this Website. 

We will not sell your personal information or give it to any third parties without your permission, unless it is to serve one of the purposes listed above. We may ask for your permission to be added to the mailing lists of our partners. 

In the event that PhraseMix is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. 

##  3\. Security 

The Personal Information we collect about you is stored on a secure, password-protected server and only authorized personnel have access to your Personal Information. We use industry-standard encryption technologies with respect to the receipt and transfer of Personal Information. Nevertheless, despite our best efforts, no transmission over the Internet or cellular network and no data storage method can be guaranteed to be safe 100% of the time. 

##  4\. Changing your account information 

You may change your account information by emailing the site administrator at [support@phrasemix.com](mailto:support@phrasemix.com) at any time. If you wish to delete or suspend your account, please email us at the same address, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 

##  5\. Unsubscribing from our mailing list 

You may unsubscribe from the PhraseMix mailing list at any time through an "Unsubscribe" link in each email that is sent to you. When you unsubscribe, we do not completely delete your email address and personal information, but you will no longer receive emails from us. 

##  6\. Unsubscribing from our mailing list 

You may unsubscribe from the PhraseMix mailing list at any time through an "Unsubscribe" link in each email that is sent to you. When you unsubscribe, we do not completely delete your email address and personal information, but you will no longer receive emails from us. 

##  7\. Data Transfers 

When we obtain personal information about you, we may process the information outside of the country in which you are located. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you are located. We will protect your information as described in this Privacy Notice. 

##  8\. Our policy toward children 

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [support@phrasemix.com](mailto:support@phrasemix.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. 

##  9\. Changes to this policy 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://www.phrasemix.com/privacy. If we make a change to this policy that we judge is important, we will notify you on the home page of the site. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

##  10\. Feedback 

We welcome any comment, question and communication at [support@phrasemix.com](mailto:support@phrasemix.com)

_Effective: March 26, 2013_
